In this session of the Autism Explained
Online Summit, our topic is combining
clinical and lived experience with Dave
Finch and Dr. Barry Present. So Barry and
Dave, what are we talking about in today's
session? We're talking about our
relationship. So if anybody wants to know
about Dave and I working together,
especially in our podcast, people should
definitely listen in. It'll be fun. It'll
be informative.
Yep, I think it's the theme of this
session is going to be complimenting and
complementary thoughts and diversity of
thought. here we have somebody who is
living
the experience, me, but very, little
academic awareness, knowledge, anything
around
autism. And kind of marrying that with Dr.
Brazant, who is not only a
legendary world class academ academician,
but has also immersed himself so deeply
and is so steeped in the true autistic
experience by just his body of work and
the
people that he chooses to spend his time
with and to learn from that it becomes a
very rich, nuanced conversation around
autism and related topics. So you should
check out this session and then you should
go listen to our podcast. So that's gonna
be a great session. Make sure you check it
out.